## Lucas Dina

lukeadina@gmail.com

# Skills & Background

Since middle school, computer programing has been more of a hobby. Nothing was serious until after high school when it was time to choose a career and I thought nothing would be better than a hobby of mine. In college, I am currently learning C# and in my free time I am playing around with many other things such as Java, Java Script, and command line based git. I hope that one day I can attain enough experience to turn one of my favorite hobby's into a full time career.

# **Experience**

August 2014 - June 2016

#### Sure Clean, 10592 West State - Wash Prep

- Prepare cars before they go through the wash. (getting tough dirt and bugs)
- Working with customers for complete satisfaction
- Working with a team to improve carwash function and overall efficiency.

June 2016 - June 2017

## BestBuy, 8363 W Franklin - Inventory Specialist

- Maintain detailed records of all products in store
- Investigate situations of missing products
- Cooperating with a team of 15 people to make sure each part of the store has the correct products
- Receiving instruction from indirect managers on how to present departments

March 2016 - PRESENT

#### AlertSense, 6149 North Meeker Place #250 - Android Developer

- Fix bugs whenever present
- Produce features in a timely manner
- Cooperating with a team of 15 people to make sure each part of the product was delivered how the customer wanted it
- Receiving instruction and following protocols to ensure product is properly working, updated, etc..

## Education

August 2012 - 2016

#### Eagle High School, 954 North Park Lane - Graduated

- Large focus on speech and debate
- Helped develop logic and reasoning skills to help in the future

# College of Western Idaho, 9300 West Overland - Sophmore

- Helped turn my hobby into something more professional
- Created challenges to test what I know and to improve upon that which I thought was satisfactory
- Currently have my code on git: <a href="https://github.com/lucasdina">https://github.com/lucasdina</a>
  - The Putlockers repo is my current personal project (Written in JavaScript)
  - The School repo has all of my assignments (written in C#)